WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Hello?
Is tony there?
No, i'm sorry,
he's not.
Who's calling?
This is mrs.
Washington
from the high school
for little anthony.
Mrs. Washington?
From your
son's school.
Hello.
Tony, it's me.
I'm sorry
to call you.
I know we
are broken up,
but my religious medal,
i look everywhere
and i think i lost it.
I think it's
on the stugots.
Oh, okay.
Who is on the
boat with you?
I'll be sure
and tell him.
Alright.
Is your son okay?
Attendance shit.
Two weeks, not eve
n a kiss hello?
I'm sorry,
yeah.
How was morocco?
Great.
Listen...
that phone call...
it was an old
girlfriend.
Oh, you mean she wasn't
from the school?
My god, she sounde
d so convincing!
I'm just trying
to be honest here.
If you're trying to be
honest, why'd you lie?
I didn't want
to piss you off.
So, it's really
more about you, then.
What are you talking
about? I didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
No, what you said
was that you didn'
t want to piss me off,
which implies that
you'd have to deal with me,
which is more abou
t sparing you than m
y fucking feelings!
Merry christmas.
Let's go with
the satin finish.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Yeah, it's me.
You know that russki,
valery, works for slava?
He owes sil
five grand.
For that oth
er thing, you know.
I need you to go
pick it up tomorrow.
Why don't sil go?
I'm sending him home
, he's dying from the flu.
I didn't
hear you, ton'.
He's sick, he's
got the flu!
I'm supposed to take my mother
to social security tomorrow.
So, you do it after.
The guy's in fairlawn.
327 dexter avenue,
number six.
I don't even
know why we deal
with these people.
You wanna guess?
They make us money.
Thank you.
And the family's well?
Honestly, i'm
a little concerned
about our daughter.
What's the problem?
She's dating a boy...
the son of some friend
s of the family actually.
I think i mentioned
him to you.
I don't know,
i guess i'm not
as optimistic
as i once was.
She was dating
a different boy,
a young
african- american man?
Yeah, they
broke up.
Actually he br
oke it off with her.
Believe that?
You didn't exactly give
him much choice, tony.
So now i'm responsible
for her being with jackie.
I'm just saying
that if you hadn't
been so mean to him
who knows, may
be she might not
be with this one.
I find it
very interesting
that you're able to ta
lk about this without rancor.
Actually we haven't been
arguing as much lately.
It's the therapy.
We're learning
how to communicate.
18 double word
score, that's 36.
No spanish.
Spanish?
Oh- bleek- ay?
Oblique.
Indirect, not
straightforward.
Come on, you're
in college.
I'm not an
english major.
As in, how'bout
giving me some?
Jackie, i'm sick.
I know, i'm
only kidding.
Unless you
want to.
Jackie.
I'm kidding,
kidding.
Wanna do
some x?
I'm already
taking nyquil.
Tired?
Actually i am
kinda wiped.
Mind if we finish
this tomorrow?
Okay.
Wow, you'r
e burning up.
I'll come by tomorrow night
and bring you some echinacea.
You're leaving?
I better let you
get some sleep.
The russians?
They're not all bad.
How about the cuban
missile crisis?
Cocksuckers moved
nuclear warheads
into cuba,
pointed'em
right at us.
That was real?
I saw that movie,
i thought it
was bullshit.
Who is?
Kgb, openup.
We didn't
wake you, did we?
Or the other 30 people
who live here?
You want?
Little early, no?
Look at this shit, tv,
stereo, dvd.
The fuck's this?
Universal remote.
Probably wiped your
ass bare handed
till you came to
this country.
So valery, you got
silvio's money?
Fucking silvio.
Watch it, comrade.
Money is on
entertainment center.
Better not be any
rubles in there.
Put remote on
docking station.
What?
Universal remote...
put down on
docking station.
Listen to this
prick giving orders.
You got some balls,
my friend.
Oops.
Paulie.
What? It was
an accident.
Ay, you want to fuck
here, cocksucker?
You come
to my house!
What'd you call me?
Paulie, paulie,
where the fuck are you?
What the fuck?
What'd you do?
What'd, i have
a choice?
I think he's dying.
Must've cracked
his windpipe.
That's it
for him.
What are you, a
fucking doctor now?
What are
we gonna do?
Pull the car around.
"I'm feeling
very sheepish."
About the other day.
I had no right to even
answer your phone.
It's alright.
I'm sorry
i lied.
You gonna open it?
It's beautiful.
It's from
morocco.
Yeah
mm- hmm.?
Now i feel like a jerk,
i got nothing for you.
Of course you do.
No, i gott
a see who this is.
Oh!
I gotta
take this.
Yeah.
Ton', it's me.
We saw that guy,
but we had a problem.
It got a
little physical.
You were just supposed
to pick up the money.
We did, but he started
giving us some shit.
The prick
sucker- punched me.
Hang on.
What?
Where are you now?
Rest sto
p, garden state.
Where's the guy?
With the luggage.
Are you fucking
kidding me?
You're breaking up,
i can't hear you.
I said, are you
fucking kidding me?
It got bad, t,
we had no choice.
I'm supposed to
meet slava later.
What the fuck
am i supposed
to say to him?
It's okay,
nobody was around.
What do you
wanna do?
You use your
own judgment.
But whatever
you decide,
you do it way the
fuck away from me,
you understand?
Motherfucker!
That was a big
waste of water.
Look, it was just
some work shit, okay?
You got ti
me for lunch?
You are my lunch.
I gotta get back.
How'bout dinner?
What do you
got in mind?
9:00, my house.
You like
london broil?
Yeah.
We could dump him
down the shore.
It's too light out
, we should wait.
They got a roy roger
s over there, you hungry?
First thing's
first, chrissy.
I know, i'm just sayin
g, i didn't eat breakfast.
Most important meal.
How you doing?
Let's take him down
to pine barrens.
That's south jersey.
It's perfect,
it's fuckin'
deserted down there.
We take him in the
woods, dig a hole,
end of story.
With fuckin' snow
all over the ground?
That's some
hard shit.
I got a shovel i use
for digging the car out.
Best part is, we'll be
like 20 minutes from a. C.
We can get a
room, freshen up,
little blackjack.
Fuck that, i gotta
eat something.
We'll go to morton's,
have a steak.
This way the day
won't be a total loss.
Things with you and carmel
a seem to be going well.
It's the therapy.
Look, i'm gonna
be honest with you.
I'm seeing somebody.
A patient of yours.
Gloria trillo.
Why gloria?
Why not?
She's smart, she's
sexy, she's italian.
Italian?
Stick to your own
kind, you know.
What is this,"west
side story" now?
Do you think havin
g met her in therapy
holds any
significance?
Maybe she reminds
me of you.
Okay.
How?
Smart, sexy,
she's italian.
She's actually
nothing like you.
Well...
maybe a little.
Who else then?
You both
got great legs.
Keep joking,
it's your dime.
Don't get jealous.
It was your fault we
met in the first place.
The scheduling
mix- up?
Point is, she
makes me happy.
Does she seem
happy to you?
When she's with me.
And you know what?
So am i.
Do you think lying
to carmela in therapy
is the best thing for
your panic attacks?
Things are going good
between me and carm,
you said so yourself.
Yeah, it's all
predicated on a lie.
Predicated on my ass,
what's the difference?
I'm content,
i'm relaxed.
The bottom line is
i'm a better husband
and a better father.
If you wanna
know the truth...
as much as i
love my wife,
being with gloria
makes me happier
than all your prozac
and your therapy bullshit
combined.
What do
you think?
I think we
should've ate.
Ya!
Cocksucker's
still alive!
Look at
this, he chewed
through the tape.
Fuckin
g piece shit!
Keep hollerin', i'
ll put one in your head.
Fuck you
fucking mother!
Get the shovel,
chrissy.
Fuckin' freezing
out here.
Hey asshole,
don't you know better
than to wear pajamas
in the middle
of winter?
Think this is
far enough?
It'll do.
The fuck
you doing?
You think we're
digging the hole?
That's right,
shit- head,
get to work.
I know
the ground's
kinda hard,
but give it some of
that siberian action.
Shut up.
The fuck's
he saying?
Who gives
a shit.
Keep digging.
Not that it
matters now,
but we didn't come to
your house to kill you.
That mouth
of yours,
you gotta learn to
shut the fuck up.
So, how far is
it to atlantic city?
Motherfucker!
Ah, fuck!
What the fuck?
I got him,
didn't i?
Yeah,
fuck!
Maybe he's
stunned.
How bad is it?
Couple of stitches,
hang on,
we'll finish him up,
we'll cover him with snow.
You see which
way he went?
He's gotta
be close.
Half his head's
probably hanging off.
There's some blood
over there.
Where is
this prick?
You sure i hit
him in the head?
Yeah, fuckin'
positive.
I don't see
any more blood.
It's like the
trail just ended.
Are you gonna be
home for dinner?
Yeah.
Alright, i'm going
to the market.
Maybe it's like
when you cut the
head off a chicken,
how they
keep runnin'.
Fuckin'
believe this?
Hello?
Where the fuck
you been?
We're down the
pine barrens.
Did you wrap
the package?
Not yet.
We were abou
t to, we had a
little problem.
What problem?
The package hit
chrissy with an
implement and ran off.
Ran off?
I thought you said
it was, you know...
we thought it was, t.
It's complicated, we'r
e looking for it now.
I can't hear you,
you're breaking up.
I said we're
looking for it.
It's like she gets sciatica,
the whole world grinds--
...could surive?
The package?
Is there any way the
package could survive?
Ton'!
Goddamnit!
Is there any
way the package
could survive?
No t, no
fucking way.
It's my life and i
'll live it any way i please.
Cocksucker!
What?
I got a meeting
with slava!
I could be
walking into a
fuckin' buzzsaw!
T, hello?
Fuck.
What'd he say?
I dunno,
he's all fucking worri
ed about this slava asshole.
I know we're doing
work with this guy.
But you gotta wonder
what tony's got going.
None of our fuckin'
business, is it?
I'm a fucking
captain.
You got a match?
My lighter's
in the car.
Mine, too.
I'm not dressed
for this shit.
He's gotta be dead
by now, right?
How could
he not be?
Fuck it,
let's just go.
Squirrels will
eat him anyway.
Where'd we park?
Back there, half
a mile or so.
You sure? 'cause
i thought we kinda
looped around.
Four years in
the army, kid.
We just follow our
own footprints, c'mon.
Wait a minute.
We walked
in a circle.
How's that
fuckin' possible?
Alright, let's
reason this out.
We were
driving south
and the sun's
setting there.
What good's
that do us?
At least we know wha
t direction we're headed.
Yeah, but we're
still fuckin' lost!
We're not lost.
Stop getting cunty.
Slava.
Tony.
Tony, come in.
Come in.
My daughte
r ilana.
Say hello
to mr. Soprano.
Hello.
How you doing?
Go to drugstor
e, buy some candy.
Beautiful girl.
Brilliant student.
One day she goes to
harvard in massachusetts,
maybe.
Family...
nothing is
more important.
That's why you
gotta plan ahead.
There's 200
in here.
Okay.
Same drill
, to isle of man,
four days,
clean as whistle.
We drink.
So, where's
your friend?
Valery?
Who knows?
He give silvio
the money, yes?
'Cause i told him.
I don't know,
i wasn't there.
Salut.
Ho, that's you and
him, ain't it?
He was like
brother to me...
closer than brother.
But now he's
tragic figure.
What do you mean?
The alcohol,
the drugs.
Disgraces to
his family.
He breaks my heart.
Maybe you could
send him to a. A.
In chechnya he
saves my life.
You're...
very emotional.
I would do
anything for him.
Take it ea
sy, we'll find it.
I'm dizzy,
my fuckin' head
is killing me.
Hello?
It's a bad connectio
n so i'm gonna talk fast.
The guy you're looking
for is some kind of
ex- commando or some shit.
He killed 16 chechen
rebels single handed.
T?
T, that you?
Ah, damnit.
I didn't hear
what you said, ton'.
It's a bad connection,
so i'm gonna talk fast.
The guy you're looking
for is an ex- commando.
He killed 16 chechen
rebels single handed.
Get the fu
ck outta here.
Yeah, nice, huh?
He was with the
interior ministry.
Guy's some kind of
russian green beret.
This guy
cannot come back
to tell this story,
you understand?
I hear you.
I'm serious, paulie.
Ton'?
Ton', you there?
Goddamn--
fuck!
Call me back!
You're not gonna
believe this.
He killed
16 czechoslovakians.
Guy was an
interior decorator.
His house
looked like shit.
Didn't you
hear it?
Twig snappin'.
You said yourself
i hit him in the head.
Fuckin' rasputin,
this guy.
See?
C'mon, he's
running.
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Fucking cunt!
Paulie, come on,
i think i got him!
If we were trying
we wouldn't have
come close.
I lost my shoe.
Hello?
It's me.
How you feeling?
Like shit.
When are you
coming over?
I gotta get my mother's
car inspected.
At night?
My friend's
a mechanic.
It's the only time
he can do it.
I'm so bummed,
i really miss you.
Can't you do
it tomorrow?
I can't.
My mother
needs thecar
and i gotta move all o
f dov's shit out of here.
I'll call
you later, okay?
Yeah, okay, bye.
This is no
fucking joke here.
I coul
d lose a foot.
It's numb, huh?
The fuck
you think?
How coul
d we be lost
like this?
We're in fucking
new jersey.
South jersey.
Maybe we should eat
some of these berries.
Are you nuts?
Shit like that
could be poisonous
, you don't know.
C'mon.
The fuck's that?
Looks like
a truck.
Ah!
There's fuckin' gravel
under this snow!
The back wheels
are gone.
Thank you, god!
My fucking ears
feel like they're
gonna fall off.
Fuck your ears.
Get me something
for my foot!
Ooh.
Jesus, that pr
ick really brained me.
I gotta sit with m
y foot under my thigh.
Use my own body heat,
that's the trick.
What if this guy's
not dead, paulie?
He's fucking dead.
I know, but 16
czechoslovakians!
He's trained
for this shit.
That's like
"die hard" shit.
I heard on the news
it's supposed to s
now again later this week.
You know the weather
report in mexico?
Chili today,
hot tamale?
You heard it
before?
Hmm.
It's an old
joke, a. J.
Egon kosma said
he made it up.
What's the matter,
you're not hungry?
Late lunch.
Could be him out
there, stalking us.
With wha
t, his cock?
Think about
it, chrissy.
Even if he's alive,
he's unarmed
and bleeding
like a sieve.
He's in the woods,
he's in his pajamas.
It's the fucking
yukon out there.
Probably thinks
we left anyway.
If he's alive,
which he ain't!
What's that?
Nathan's bag.
There's some
ketchups and shit.
They clean?
I dunno, they
were in the bag.
They were a little
half- way frozen.
Fuck it,
gimme some.
Here.
Not bad.
Mix it with
the relish.
It's nana
and grandpa.
Ma, what are y
ou guys doing here?
Three hours at
the eye doctor.
Glaucoma.
I may need
an operation.
Oh, my god.
C'mon,
sit down.
You hungry,
you want to eat?
Who could eat after
news like that?
I'll make
some coffee.
Hello.
It's me.
Where are you?
We're still here.
And?
No good.
That's really
fuckin' great.
That language,
is that necessary?
Listen ton',
we're really lost.
We been walking
around for hours.
I lost my shoe.
We found
some old truck.
A truck.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
How'bout some advice?
What?
How'bout
some advice?
You want my advice?
You stay there till
the morning and then
you find this guy.
We're trying!
Goddamn
fucking phone!
Thanks, to
n', thanks a lot.
Oh, i should be
happy about this?
No, it's just...
your nephew,
sometimes he don't
think before he acts.
That's all
i'm gonna say.
I thought the guy
sucker punched you.
He did.
It's just...
we'll talk later.
You're having
coffee, right?
My father
has glaucoma.
It's jackie,
leave a message.
It's me again.
You said you
were gonna call.
Where the hell
are you?
Hi ambujam,
i'm really sorry,
i need to
borrow your car.
If i wanted to be treated
like shit i'd get married.
I'm sorry.
Something came up.
Dinner is
fucking ruined.
We'll go out.
Anywhere
you want.
C'mon, don't
be like that.
Inconsiderate prick.
I said i
was sorry.
It was
family shit.
It couldn't
be avoided.
Let me make it
up to you.
You were supposed
to be here three
hours ago.
I know.
I'm here now
, aren't i?
Hmm?
This is fucking
bullshit!
It was silvio's
money, he should've
got it himself!
Cocksucker got
the sniffles,
and we're
stuck out here!
You shouldn't
have hit the guy.
I shouldn't have
even been there!
Fuckin' insult
he even gives
me this shit,
your uncle.
Yeah, blame
tony now.
You had to hear him
on the phone before.
Talking to me
like a child.
You have any idea
the money i made for
him over the years?
Or his old man
before him?
He's living like
a fucking king
and now all i hear about
is cocksucker ralphie.
I'm going to sleep.
Let me get some
of that carpet.
I been working
on a plan.
A plan?
We're in a
truck, right?
It had to get
here somehow,
there's gotta
be a road out.
It's grown over,
it stops at
those trees.
Give me your shoes,
i can go get help.
Fuck you,
you're not
leaving me here.
You don't trust me?
It's stupid,
pitch dark out there.
And what's
your fucking plan?
Eat ketchup packs?
We should've stopped
at roy rogers!
And i shouldn't fucked
dale evans, but i didn't!
What are you doing?
Calling tony again.
You're gonna
piss him
off, paulie.
Fuck him!
We're gonna
die out here.
Oh, fuck!
Yeah.
It's me.
What now?
Chrissy's head is bleeding
and i'm freezing to death,
that's what's
fucking now.
Hey, take it easy!
I'm through
taking it easy.
We're fucking
starving out here.
What do you want
me to do about it?
Come fucking
get us!
You don't even know
where the fuck you are!
Exit 12.
What?
Exit fuckin' 12.
Pike's hollow
or some shit.
Pike's hollow.
There's a dirt roa
d at the turnoff.
We're parked
about a mile in
near some
picnic tables.
And when i find the
car, then what?
I don't know,
start yellin'!
We're in a truck.
That dirt road might be
the same one we're on.
Put my nephew
on the phone.
Here.
Yeah, t.
Are you alright?
I don't know, my
head's killing me.
I can't hear you.
My head hurts,
i think i got
a concussion.
Alright,
just stay calm.
Bring some food,
alright?
Some fucki
ng shoes, too.
Alright,
hang in there.
I gotta go.
What, are you
kidding me?
It's an emergency.
What do you
want from me?
think, i'm some
fucking whore?
Just calm down.
You think you're
just gonna come over
here and fuck me?
You know what?
I don't got time
for this shit.
Oh, now you're gonna leave,
you low- life piece of shit!
You know
what? Here!
Take your
fucking dinner!
I fucking
hate you!
I know he's
cheating on me.
I could hear it
in his voice.
Car inspection?
It's bullshit.
What if he's
not though?
Doing this would make
me as bad as he is.
Maybe we
should go.
Hey.
Sorry i had
to wake you.
Fucking chemo.
I'm awake throwing
up half the night anyway.
Did you
call bobby?
He's on his way.
What've you
been eating, steak?
No--
i dunno.
I need to
borrow a shirt.
You want
some tea?
No.
Fuck this!
Where you going?
It's not bad enough
you wake me in the
middle of the night.
I gotta get my balls
broken too?
Go with my nephew,
do what he says.
I gotta
change my shirt.
I got my limits
too, jr.
Be strong.
You have a good time?
Me, too.
What are you
doing tomorrow?
Yeah, of
course i did.
I can't believe
you did this to me.
What are you
doing here?
I loved you.
Who the hell
are you?
Fuck you,
bitch.
What'd you say?
Don't ever
call me again!
Meadow, wait.
Yeah, you better
leave, bitch!
What the fuck is the
matter with you?
That's tony soprano's
daughter!
Oh, what do
i care, asshole?
Fuckin' bitch.
Goddamnit!
You really know
about this shit?
The woods
and hunting?
My dad and me used
to go every year.
I'm sorry i laughe
d at you before.
It's alright.
One time we
went hunting...
we saw a sign that
said,"bear left,"
so we went home.
I want you to know
i appreciate you
taking care of my uncle.
Yeah, i know.
He really loves you,
you know that?
C'mon, that old prick?
I'm serious.
He talks about
you all the time.
I know you had your
problems but, i dunno...
i wish he was my
uncle sometimes.
What time is it?
4:30.
Where the
fuck is he?
What are those,
tic- tacs?
I just found'em.
I didn't know
i had'em on me.
You had tic- tacs all
along? Give me some!
There ain't no
more, i ate'em.
Selfish prick,
i'm dying here!
Then fucking
die already.
Where you going
? don't go out there!
I'm eating
those berries.
I'm telling you,
they're poison!
I don't give a
shit, at least i
won't die hungry.
You sure this is
the right place?
Yeah,
pike's hollow.
One mile in, by
the picnic table.
Where's their
car, though?
Maybe they left.
They wouldn't leave
without calling.
Let me try
him again.
Tony?
Paulie, we're by the...
ton', i can't hear you!
We're gonna...
motherfucking
cocksucker!
That tony
? what'd he say?
I don't know!
Ho!
Do that by
your own window!
I don't wanna
smell your piss.
Fuck you.
What did you say?
You heardme.
Don't make me pull
rank on you, kid.
Fuck you,
paulie.
Captain
or no captain,
right now we're
just two assho
les lost in the woods.
Do yourself a favor,
chrissy and go back
to fucking sleep!
Why, so you could
choke me?
What?
You thin
k i'm stupid.
I heard you on
the phone trying to
blame this on me.
The fuck you
talking about?
You fucked up wi
th the russian prick,
now you're
worried about tony.
You'll wai
t till i'm asleep,
then you'll choke me,
so he'll just have
your version.
Choke you right
now, you fuck!
I'll leave you here,
you one- shoe cocksucker!
Put it down,
chrissy.
You know how fast
i can run.
I'll leave you
in the fucking dust!
All the shit
we been through.
You think i'd
really kill you?
Yeah, i do.
Promise me you won't
leave me here.
I'm not gonna
leave you.
Paulie!
Christopher!
What do you think,
what should we do?
There's nothing
we can do.
We'll wait
till it's light,
then we'll
head in.
1- 0- 1.
Let's get some
fluids in you,
we'll send you
home later.
Oh, my god,
are you okay?
She was out
all night, i
couldn't stop her.
It's over.
He was cheating on me.
Holy shit.
We drove out
to jersey,
i caught them together.
She was a real
whore, too.
Oh, my god.
That's horrible.
It's all
my fault.
I shouldn't
have pressured
him like that.
You're bet
ter off without
him, meadow.
I mean
, he was cute,
but he was
really boring.
You didn't know
him like i did.
You don't know what it's like
to grow up where we did!
Whatever, mead,
he was such a drip.
No, me wasn't,
he was great!
Bruno magli
over here.
Which way, wha
t do you think?
Don't matter
to me.
I ain't stopping
till we hit cement.
A lotta strange
people used to
live in these woods.
Jackson whites,
these weird
looking albinos.
Paulie!
Christopher!
First place i'm
hitting is denny's.
I know.
Get like five of those
grand slam breakfasts.
Shit!
What's the matter?
Fucking thing'
s loose already.
Motherfucker!
What are
you doing?
What if we need
the bullets?
That's n
o deer hunter.
Paulie!
Christopher!
Tony!
Over here!
Paulie!
Christopher!
Where are you?
Over here, tony!
Thank fuckin' god!
You guys
alright?
What the f
uck you shootin' at?
Nothing,
never mind.
Jesus christ,
look at you two!
All night in this
fuckin' hell hole.
Alright, c'mon.
C'mon, easy.
Is this
the spot?
Yeah, but...
my fucking
car's gone.
You sure this is
where you left it?
I'm positive.
Is the
heat on?
Jesus christ, i
can't feel my toes.
You got any
blankets?
No, sorry.
Turn up the
heat, huh?
I can't
believe it,
i fuckin'
loved that car.
Probably kids
or something.
What if it
was the guy?
You got the money?
It was in the car.
That's all i asked
you to do, paulie.
I'm sorry, t, it
couldn't be helped.
The guy fuckin'
lunged at us.
Listen, ton', i know
i fucked up, but--
it's okay,
really.
Just forget it.
What do you think,
you wanna look for
this guy or what?
You tell me.
Is it worth it?
I hit him in
the head, ton'.
I saw it with
my own eyes.
Is it possible this fu
ck made it outta here alive?
It's hard to say.
Flesh wound maybe,
head shot, i don't know.
On the other hand,
anything's possible.
You're a captain,
what do you wanna do?
Fuck it,
let's go home.
Alright.
But let's be clear
on this right now.
If this cocksucker
crawls out from
under a rock
he's your problem,
not mine.
You deal with slava,
you take the heat,
you pay the price.
Capisce?
Fine.
You got mayonnaise
on your chin.
What?
Mayonnaise,
mayonnaise!
I'm telling
you, something's
fucked up here.
Because one minute
she's fine,
next minute she's a
fuckin' lunatic!
I asked you
whether or not
she seemed like
a happy person.
Oh, and by tha
t i'm supposed to know
she's gonna throw
a fuckin' roast
beef at my head?
Read into things
however you choose.
Why does everything
gotta be so hard?
I'm not saying
i'm perfect,
but i do the right
thing by my family.
Doesn't that
count for anything?
I think we
should discuss
what attracted you to
gloria in the first place.
We been through
that already.
And irina
before her.
Depressive
personality,
unstable,
impossible to please.
Does that remind you
of any other woman?
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.